

Joe Alt Front end developer

About Me

I'm a full stack, front end oriented developer who's passionate for creating innovative and visually appealing websites.

Collaboration is key for me, and I enjoy working with others to achieve the best results.

My strengths include being dedicated, fast learning and hardworking. I'm also someone how makes 100% use of the 4 years of experience in JavaScript I own, the eager to learn and improve, and working to get into a challenging work environment that allows me to grow as a professional.

Education Background

Master in Software Development
 Assembler Institute of Technology
 October 2022 - May 2023

Languages

- Dutch Native
- English Fluent
- Spanish Fluent

My Contact

+34 644 65 39 74

🧹 joejoyalt@gmail.com

github.com/joejoyjoy

n linkedin.com/in/joe-alt

• Málaga, Spain Open to work onsite or remote

Dutch nationality. Spanish NIE

Professional Experience

Full Stack Developer | Assembler Institute of Technology October 2022 - May 2023

Intensive 7-month master in software development. More than 1200 hours of full stack real-world oriented projects with Agile methodology based on "Learn by doing" and pair programming, focusing on up to date strong fundamentals. Three of the many projects done:

Audity | React.js, TypeScript, Node.js, Express and MongoDB Click here (2)

Music platform inspired by Spotify with all the key features as listening, create playlists, upload songs add to favoriets among other things. It's a PWA, mobile friendly and with admin panel to control the content.

GitHub Ultimate | React.js, TypeScript, Node.js and GraphQL Click here Company Login though Github OAuth app to show user repos with search and sort functions called from GitHub GraphQL API with unit Jest testing.

To Do List | React.js, SASS, Node.js and MongoDB

Click here r₹

Contains login authentication together with Node.js and express backend for all CRUD functions called from frontend with fetch RESTful API and mobile friendly with styled-components for the styling.

Web developer | for 5 businesses which two of them: 2017 - 2022

Andalusia Health Retreats | Wix

Click here [3

Website for an organization of vacation retreats for groups or individuals. I'm proudly the web developer and implemented payment methods and a filter/sorting system with JavaScript for the venues they offer. All with great SEO

Massages and Wellness at home | Wix

Click here 🖸

Website about massagist portfolio, history and contact options if interested in booking a session. Seamless integration with appointments implemented through the calender and a list of all possible massages available. Adding google analytics and maps

Tech Skills

Front end

HTML5, CSS3, JS, SASS, React, TS, Styled Components and CSS-modules

Back end

PHP, Node.js, Express and Laravel

Database

MySQL and MongoDB

Tools

Git, API RESTful, Scrum/Agile, Auth0, Jest and Cypress testing, Bootstrap, Figma, ClickUp, Cloudinary, Postman, VSCode and MVC

Soft Skills

Creative • Observant • Decision maker • Adaptable • Dedicated • Team work • Problem Solver • Commitment

Courses

- Affiliate Marketing
- Udemy HTML, CSS, JS
- · Gimp photoshop
- DaVinci Resolve video editor



























8

Figma